Hey 아까부터 널 봤어
우린 처음이지만 모든 재미를 느낄 수 있어 더 알고 싶어
Hey 웃지만 말고 말이야
가본 적이 없는 곳에 너를 데려가 줄게
Come with me, put it on put it on me
You got this, put it on put it on me
결국 내 손을 잡을 거야
‘Cause I know that you’ve been dreaming
마치 천국의 deja vu
지금부터 난 널 만나 Interview
네가 원한 모든 걸 다 줄 수가 있어
너의 어두운 모습까지도
Come come into my world
Won’t let you down
내게로 와
In my in my in my new world
Knock knock knockin’ on heaven’s door
Whipped cream cloud 손끝으로 쓸어
내 All star 밑에 딛고 날아 sunset
넘 빠름 I’ma take it slow
슬픔이 없는 곳에서 이대로 춤을 춰
박자에 맞춰 박수
넌 영원을 내게 줘 기쁨의 맛을 더
영원에 영원을 더 더 더 더
Come with me, put it on put it on me
You got this, put it on put it on me
결국 내 손을 잡을 거야
‘Cause I know that you’ve been dreaming
마치 천국의 deja vu
지금부터 난 널 만나 Interview
네가 원한 모든 걸 다 줄 수가 있어
너의 어두운 모습까지도
Come come into my world
Won’t let you down
내게로 와
In my in my in my new world
We got the heart we got the soul
이대로 우리 맘을 열어
너에게 넌 나에게
새로운 미래를 열어줘 나 손을 놓지 않을게
Trust in me baby I can see
마치 천국의 deja vu
지금부터 난 널 만나 Interview
네가 원한 모든 걸 다 줄 수가 있어
너의 어두운 모습까지도
Come come into my world
Won’t let you down
내게로 와
In my in my in my new world